{
    "subject": "resource/10_Questions_for_the_Dalai_Lama",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicComposer",
    "object": "resource/Peter_Kater",
    "human_readable": "The music composer of 10 Questions for the Dalai Lama is Peter Kater.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9724183678627014,
            "question": "Who composed the music for '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8481615781784058,
            "question": "What instruments are featured in '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8061696290969849,
            "question": "Are there any other notable works by Peter Kater besides '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7818560600280762,
            "question": "Where can one listen to '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.715194582939148,
            "question": "What genre of music does Peter Kater typically compose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6278034448623657,
            "question": "Is Peter Kater known for composing music for film or other media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5724092125892639,
            "question": "What is the overall tone or mood of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5622303485870361,
            "question": "What is the name of the musical piece associated with Peter Kater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3338235914707184,
            "question": "Has Peter Kater won any awards for his compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31345412135124207,
            "question": "How does Peter Kater's music reflect his personal beliefs or experiences?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music composer of 10 Questions for the Dalai Lama is Peter Kater.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3712_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Peter Kater won any awards for his compositions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3712_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the musical piece associated with Peter Kater?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3712_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall tone or mood of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3712_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3712_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports the statement. Specifically, in `12.txt` and `25.txt`, it mentions \"Peter Kater \u2013 10 Questions for the Dalai Lama\" and in `2.txt`, it states \"Original music score by Peter Kater.\" These details confirm that Peter Kater is indeed the composer of the soundtrack for \"10 Questions for the Dalai Lama\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}